Shen Tianyi has lost his Soulstone
لقد فقد شين تيان يي حجر روحه
His body is rapidly aging
جسده يتقدم في السن بسرعة
Now what he wants most is you
الآن ما يريده أكثر هو أنت
And this is also your best chance
وهذه أيضًا أفضل فرصة لك
Actually I've never understood
في الواقع لم أفهم أبدا
You so devoutly believe in your Lord
أنت تؤمن بربك بشدة
Yet when we struggle like ants
ومع ذلك عندما نكافح مثل النمل
Fighting desperately to survive
القتال بشدة من أجل البقاء
What exactly is your Lord doing?
ماذا يفعل ربك بالضبط؟
Suffering
معاناة
Makes one question if they took the wrong path
يثير سؤالا واحدا عما إذا كانوا قد اتخذوا الطريق الخطأ
But can also guide them back
ولكن يمكن أيضا أن يرشدهم إلى الوراء
The Lord
الرب
Will wipe away their tears
سوف يمسح دموعهم
There'll be no more death
لن يكون هناك المزيد من الموت
Nor sorrow
ولا حزن
Crying
بكاء
Or pain
أو الألم
For the former things have
لأن الأشياء السابقة قد
Passed away
توفي
Those not in the Tome of Destinies
أولئك الذين ليسوا في كتاب الأقدار
Shall be cast into the fiery lake
سوف يُلقى في البحيرة النارية
It seems Mr. Meng
يبدو أن السيد منغ
Is quite familiar with scripture
هو على دراية تامة بالكتاب المقدس
In my days of suffering
في أيام معاناتي
I swore to heaven
لقد أقسمت بالسماء
I'd destroy the wicked with my own hands
سأدمر الأشرار بيدي
Turn their laughter to weeping
حوّل ضحكهم إلى بكاء
Reduce their strongholds to ashes
حوّل حصونهم إلى رماد
How many do we have now?
كم لدينا الآن؟
Miss
يفتقد
Counting all in the Jia household
عد كل شيء في منزل جيا
Twenty-three remain
بقي ثلاثة وعشرون
Summon them all
استدعيهم جميعا
Even the kitchen helpers?
حتى مساعدي المطبخ؟
Did I stutter? Everyone means everyone!
هل تلعثمتُ؟ الكل يعني الكل!
Why look at him?
لماذا ننظر إليه؟
I'm in charge here
أنا المسؤول هنا
Yuer
يوير
Enough
كافٍ
You're coming too
أنت قادم أيضا
When everyone's gathered
عندما يجتمع الجميع
We storm Shen's house together
اقتحمنا منزل شين معًا
Agreed
متفق
We'll follow your lead
سوف نتبع خطاك
Why so quick to agree?
لماذا هذه السرعة في الموافقة؟
Meng Yan's a good boy
منغ يان هو فتى جيد
And most importantly
والأهم من ذلك
He's my future nephew-in-law
إنه ابن أخي المستقبلي
If I won't save my own kin
إذا لم أنقذ أقاربي
What kind of uncle would I be?
أي نوع من العم أريد أن أكون؟
What nonsense!
ما هذا الهراء!
You kept this from me so long
لقد أخفيت هذا عني لفترة طويلة
I haven't settled with you yet
لم أستقر معك بعد
After we save Meng Yan
بعد أن أنقذنا منغ يان
We'll settle accounts then
سوف نقوم بتسوية الحسابات بعد ذلك
Why so few of you?
لماذا عدد قليل منكم؟
Where are the rest?
أين الباقي؟
From now on
من الآن فصاعدا
Keep Yuer securely at home
احفظ يوير في المنزل بشكل آمن
If she escapes
إذا هربت
I'll hold you responsible
سأحملك المسؤولية
Jia Yaozu
جيا ياوزو
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Jia Yaozu, you jerk!
جيا ياوزو، أيها الأحمق!
Sorry Yuer
آسف يوير
The older generation's business
أعمال الجيل الأكبر سنا
Should stay with them
ينبغي أن يبقى معهم
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Jia Yaozu
جيا ياوزو
Jia Yaozu, what are you doing?
جيا ياوزو، ماذا تفعل؟
Come back!
عد!
Jia Yaozu, stop this!
جيا ياوزو، أوقف هذا!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Jia Yaozu
جيا ياوزو
So I'm being locked up again?
إذن أنا محتجز مرة أخرى؟
I can't watch you march to your death
لا أستطيع أن أشاهدك تسير نحو موتك
I know you're worried
أعلم أنك قلق
But Meng Yan...
لكن منغ يان...
I'll keep him safe
سأبقيه آمنًا
You have my word
لديك كلمتي
Then be careful, mother
إذن كن حذرا يا أمي
Are you certain, Madam Tang?
هل أنت متأكدة سيدتي تانغ؟
Entering here today
الدخول هنا اليوم
Against Shen Tianyi
ضد شين تيان يى
Means fight to the death
يعني القتال حتى الموت
Are you afraid?
هل انت خائف؟
I do fear
انا خائف
Never seeing your graceful self again
لن ترى نفسك الرشيقة مرة أخرى
Then let's turn back
ثم دعونا نعود
We're already here
نحن هنا بالفعل
You...
أنت...
All your abilities and progress
جميع قدراتك وتقدمك
Have been under my control
لقد كانت تحت سيطرتي
Don't be arrogant, Meng Yan
لا تكن متغطرسًا، منغ يان
Our understanding of power
فهمنا للقوة
Was never the same
لم يكن نفسه أبدًا
Let me show you
دعني أريك
What true power is
ما هي القوة الحقيقية
You
أنت
The means you've employed
الوسائل التي استخدمتها
to surpass and defeat me
لتتفوق علي وتهزمني
are proof of your efforts and strength
هي دليل على جهودك وقوتك
And those very means
وتلك الوسائل ذاتها
represent the measure of your hope
تمثل مقياس أملك
What I shall do now
ماذا سأفعل الآن
is utterly crush that hope
إنه سحق تماما هذا الأمل
Dust to be swept away
الغبار الذي يجب إزالته
whether one speck or two
سواء كانت بقعة واحدة أو اثنتين
makes no difference
لا يوجد فرق
to the eye
إلى العين
The two family heads visiting Shen Manor
رئيسا العائلتين يزوران قصر شين
Shen failed to properly receive you
لقد فشل شين في استقبالك بشكل صحيح
I came today
لقد جئت اليوم
to settle accounts
لتسوية الحسابات
with the Shen family
مع عائلة شين
Father
أب
Mother
الأم
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Father
أب
Mother
الأم
Yan'er
يانير
We must leave now
يجب علينا أن نغادر الآن
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Yan'er
يانير
Your mother and I
أنا وأمك
never wanted you in the Gifted's world
لم أكن أريدك أبدًا في عالم الموهوبين
Yet you've walked this path regardless
ومع ذلك فقد مشيت في هذا الطريق بغض النظر عن ذلك
We meant to let you grow naturally
لقد قصدنا أن نسمح لك بالنمو بشكل طبيعي
But seeing you suffer each time
لكن رؤيتك تعاني في كل مرة
our hearts would cry out
قلوبنا ستصرخ
and waver
وتردد
leaning toward
يميل نحو
helping you gain greater power
مساعدتك على اكتساب قوة أكبر
rather than stopping you becoming Gifted
بدلاً من منعك من أن تصبح موهوبًا
Yan'er
يانير
You've grown strong
لقد أصبحت قويا
So even as we depart
لذلك حتى عندما نغادر
we rejoice for you
نحن نفرح من أجلك
We've always been by your side
لقد كنا دائما بجانبك
watching you grow
مشاهدتك تنمو
and were truly happy
وكانوا سعداء حقا
Yan'er
يانير
We are content
نحن راضون
Father
أب
Mother
الأم
Never
أبداً
has anyone stood above
هل وقف أحد فوق
Shen Tianyi
شين تيان يى
Not the Tangs
ليس التانغ
nor the Jias
ولا جياس
Not even the Mengs
ولا حتى المينجس
Madam Tang
السيدة تانغ
Continuing like this
استمرار على هذا النحو
we'll all be exhausted to death
سوف نكون جميعا مرهقين حتى الموت
Now
الآن
there's only one way
هناك طريقة واحدة فقط
What way?
أي طريق؟
We release all our spiritual energy
نحن نطلق كل طاقتنا الروحية
to breach his power's limits
لخرق حدود قوته
and make him explode
وجعله ينفجر
Agreed
متفق
We'll perish together
سوف نهلك معا
Now!
الآن!